Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 10 and District 10 Locals, 1936-1994 UE.4.1.10
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 10 Locals, 2.
  - Local 1007
    - Local 1007 Per Capita, August 23-October 19, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Local 1007 Separate Charter, 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - William Elconin to Julius Emspak, November 13, 1950; 1.
      - Sandra Waite to General Executive Board, December 4, 1950; 2.
      - Petition, December 1950; 3.
      - Emspak to Waite, December 6, 1950; 4.
      - Emspak to Waite, March 26, 1951; 5.
      - Emspak to Waite, April 10, 1951; 6.
      - Notice of Issued Charter, June 1, 1951; 7.
      - David Scribner to Waite, July 23, 1951; 8.
      - Emspak to Scribner, July 1951; 9.
      - Emspak to Joseph Houseman, July 24, 1951; 10.
      - Memo, July 24, 1951; 11.
    - Local 1007 Correspondence, 1952-1955 (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - William Elconin to Joseph Dermody with Letter Excerpts, January 9, 1952; 1.
      - Address Change, August 29, 1955; 2.
  - Local 1008
    - Local 1008 Incoming Correspondence, 1951-1956 (Box 3, Folder 39)
      - Julius Emspak to Phillip Falker Regarding Organization, July 21, 1951; 1.
      - Emspak to Dawn Collins, September 14, 1953; 2.
      - Emspak to James Yamaguchi Regarding Finances, August 10, 1955; 3.
      - Emspak to Floyd Turner Regarding Strikes, November 29, 1955; 4.
      - Emspak to Turner Regarding Strikes, December 9, 1955; 5.
      - Emspak to Henry Hale Regarding Strikes, December 20, 1955; 6.
      - Emspak to Yamaguchi Regarding Strikes, January 3, 1956; 7.
      - Emspak to Hale Regarding Strikes, January 10, 1956; 8.
      - Emspak to Hale Regarding Strikes, January 23, 1956; 9.
      - Emspak to Yamaguchi Regarding Strikes, February 8, 1956; 10.
      - Emspak to Yamaguchi Regarding Strikes, February 15, 1956; 11.
      - Emspak to Yamaguchi Regarding Strikes, February 21, 1956; 12.
      - Emspak to Yamaguchi Regarding Strikes, February 29, 1956; 13.
      - Emspak to Yamaguchi Regarding Strikes, March 2, 1956; 14.
      - Emspak to Yamaguchi Regarding Strikes, March 7, 1956; 15.
      - Emspak to Yamaguchi Regarding Strikes, March 14, 1956; 16.
      - Emspak to Members Regarding Strikes and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, April 25, 1956; 17.
    - Local 1008 Outgoing Correspondence, 1953-1956, undated (Box 3, Folder 40)
      - Dawn Collins to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, September 1953; 1.
      - Collins to James Matles Regarding Dues and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, 2.
      - Henry Hale to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Strikes and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, March 23, 1956; 3.
      - James Yamaguchi to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, September 11, 1953; 4.
    - Local 1008 Chartering, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 41)
      - Julius Emspak to William Elconin, June 8, 1951; 1.
      - Emspak to Elconin, June 27, 1951; 2.
      - Notice of Issued Charter, June 27, 1951; 3.
      - Joe Housemann to Emspak, July 5, 1951; 4.
      - Research Memo, July 1951; 5.
      - Emspak to Housmann, July 19, 1951; 6.
    - Local 1008 Strike, 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - William Elconin to James Matles, November 23, 1955; 1.
      - Matles to Charles Newell, November 29, 1955; 2.
      - Matles to Newell, December 9, 1955; 3.
      - Julius Emspak to Newell, December 20, 1955; 4.
      - Matles to Newell, January 3, 1956; 5.
      - Matles to Newell, January 4, 1956; 6.
      - Emspak to Newell, February 21, 1956; 7.
      - Emspak to Newell, March 2, 1956; 8.
      - Emspak to Newell, March 7, 1956; 9.
    - Local 1008 Correspondence and Report, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 43)
      - William Elconin to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances and International Brotherhood of Electical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, September 10, 1953; 1.
      - Bill Santora Report, December 14, 1953; 2.
    - Local 1008 710 Forms, 1951-1960 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Local 1009
    - Local 1009 Incoming Correspondence, Julius Emspak to H.R. Pecot Regarding Organization, December 8, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Local 1009 Outgoing Correspondence, H.R. Pecot to Al Stonkus Regarding Organization, December 1, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Local 1009 Per Capita Reports, December 1937-April 1938 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Local 1009 Notices of Delinquency and Suspension, February-May 1938 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Local 1009 Leaflets, 1938, undated (Box 3, Folder 49)
      - "Special Meeting", January 1938; 1.
      - "What's Wrong With This Picture", March 25, 1938; 2.
      - "The Undersigned" Regarding Negotiations, 3.
      - "General Membership Meeting", n.d.; 4.
    - Local 1009 Correspondence, Julius Emspak to Verne Kennedy Regarding Per Capita, July 16, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Local 1009 Anaheim General Electric and Correspondence, 1977-1982 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Local 1009 (Salt Lake City)
    - Local 1009 (Salt Lake City) Incoming Correspondence, Julius Emspak to Dora Walker Regarding Organization, October 6, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Local 1009 (Salt Lake City) Outgoing Correspondence, Howard Lee to Norma Gould Regarding Organization, undated (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Local 1009 (Salt Lake City) Per Capita Report, April 7, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Local 1009 (Salt Lake City) Organization, 1943-1955 (Box 3, Folder 55)
      - Frank Bonacci to Albert Fitzgerald, August 24, 1943; 1.
      - Bonacci to Julius Emspak, September 1, 1943; 2.
      - Bonacci to Emspak, September 2, 1943; 3.
      - Emspak to Bonacci, October 6, 1943; 4.
      - Emspak to Martin Hourihan, October 6, 1943; 5.
      - Emspak to Marcella Ryan, December 27, 1943; 6.
      - Ryan to Emspak, December 31, 1943; 7.
      - Clarence Palmer to Elbert Thomas, March 14, 1948; 8.
      - Memo, April 5, 1944; 9.
      - Ryan to Emspak, April 7, 1944; 10.
      - Bonacci to Emspak, July 25, 1955; 11.
      - Bonacci to Emspak, September 12, 1945; 12.
  - Local 1010
    - Local 1010 Leaflet, undated (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Local 1010 Ontario, CA, 1963-1967 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Local 1011
    - Local 1011 Incoming Correspondence, 1939-1942 (Box 3, Folder 58)
      - Carl Bersing to Local 1011 Regarding Exide Kansas City Organization, January 26, 1942; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Carl Knutson Regarding Singer Strike, July 7, 1939; 2.
      - Emspak to E. Buhle Regarding Mine Mill Strike, March 2, 1942; 3.
      - James Matles to E. Friberg Regarding Radio Conference and Wages, October 7, 1941; 4.
    - Local 1011 Outgoing Correspondence, 1939-1942 (Box 3, Folder 59)
      - Peter Apel to James Matles Regarding Negotiations, March 13, 1941; 1.
      - G.J. Buhle to Julius Emspak Regarding Officers, October 2, 1939; 2.
      - Buhle to Emspak Regarding Officers, February 9, 1940; 3.
      - Buhle to Emspak Regarding Mine Mill Strike, February 10, 1942; 4.
      - E. Friberg to UE Regarding Officers, June 1941; 5.
      - Walter Joseph to Charles Goff Regarding Negotiations, April 30, 1940; 6.
      - Carl Knutson to Emspak Regarding Local 917 Strike, June 29, 1939; 7.
      - L. Ollis to UE Regarding Officers, February 3, 1941; 8.
    - Local 1011 Amalgamation, 1942-1943 (Box 3, Folder 60)
      - Julius Emspak to Carl Brant, November 3, 1942; 1.
      - Emspak to Brant, February 9, 1943; 2.
    - Local 1011 Correspondence, 1939-1941 (Box 3, Folder 61)
      - Leo Turner to Julius Emspak Regarding Organization, April 1, 1939; 1.
      - Turner to J.M. Jacobs Regarding Negotiations, May 31, 1939; 2.
      - Turner to Matles Regarding Wages, July 20, 1939; 3.
      - Carl Bersing to Turner Regarding Negotiations, April 1, 1941; 4.
  - Local 1012
    - Local 1012 Membership Resolution Regarding Red-baiting, October 5, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Local 1012 Incoming Correspondence, 1943-1955 (Box 3, Folder 63)
      - Bill Cahn to Robert Miller Regarding Local Newspaper, March 13, 1947; 1.
      - Joseph Dermody to J.V. Brashear Regarding Negotiations, October 19, 1951; 2.
      - Dermody to Brashear Regarding Negotiations, October 20, 1951; 3.
      - Julius Emspak to Ernest Wildeman Regarding Bonding, July 22, 1942; 4.
      - Emspak to Robert Miller Regarding Negotiations, July 7, 1943; 5.
      - Emspak to Miller Regarding Negotiations, July 27, 1943; 6.
      - Emspak to Thomas Kirkland Regarding Quinn-Emspak Case, May 31, 1955; 7.
      - Emspak to Gertrude Southern Regarding Westinghouse Strike, December 13, 1955; 8.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to W.H. Tangeman Regarding Productivity, January 18, 1943; 9.
      - Fitzgerald to J.F. Spillane Regarding European Tour, May 18, 1951; 10.
      - Leo Jandreau to Miller Regarding War Labor Board Negotiations, July 21, 1943; 11.
      - Jandreau to Miller Regarding Grievances, October 21, 1943; 12.
      - Jandreau to Miller Regarding Negotiations and Vacations, November 8, 1943; 13.
      - Jandreau to Miller Regarding Overtime, November 11, 1943; 14.
      - Jandreau to Miller Regarding Negotiations, January 25, 1944; 15.
      - Jandreau to Miller Regarding Grievances, March 2, 1944; 16.
    - Local 1012 Incoming Correspondence, 1943-1954 (Box 3, Folder 64)
      - James Matles to W.H. Tangeman Regarding Productivity, January 15, 1943; 1.
      - Matles to G.E. Lindsey Regarding Matles Visit, December 3, 1948; 2.
      - Matles to Bob Miller Regarding Skilled Workers, Negotiations, and Wage Stabilization Board, January 23, 1952; 3.
      - Matles to Miller Regarding Skilled Workers, June 12, 1952; 4.
      - Matles to Jacuelyn Mann Regarding Finances, July 30, 1953; 5.
      - Matles to Eugene Sole Regarding Finances, March 8, 1954; 6.
      - Matles to Henry Ranch Regarding Finances and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, June 17, 1954; 7.
      - Matles to Thomas Kirkland Regarding Education, December 9, 1954; 8.
    - Local 1012 Outgoing Correspondence, 1943-1955 (Box 3, Folder 65)
      - J.U. Brashear to Joseph Dermody Regarding Negotiations, May 3, 1948; 1.
      - Brashear to Dermody Regarding Grievances, October 24, 1952; 2.
      - Brashear to James Matles Regarding Grievances, November 14, 1952; 3.
      - Andrew Conahan to Matles Regarding Productivity with Production Awards Invitation, January 4, 1943; 4.
      - Conahan to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Production with Production Awards Invitation, January 4, 1943; 5.
      - Conahan to Julius Emspak Regarding Contract, April 7, 1943; 6.
      - Thomas Kirkland to Matles Regarding Education, Factionalism, and Staff Members, December 2, 1954; 7.
      - Kirkland to Fitzgerald Regarding Ontario Visit, April 12, 1955; 8.
      - Jacquelyn Mann to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, September 11, 1953; 9.
      - Robert Miller to Emspak Regarding U.S. Bonds, April 14, 1943; 10.
    - Local 1012 Outgoing Correspondence, 1943-1955 (Box 3, Folder 66)
      - Robert Miller to UE Regarding Overtime, October 31, 1943; 1.
      - Miller to UE Regarding Medical Benefits and Overtime, November 22, 1943; 2.
      - Miller to UE Regarding Stewards, January 1944; 3.
      - Miller to Leo Jandreau Regarding Women, February 23, 1944; 4.
      - Miller to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Fitzgerald Visit, Seniority, and Grievances, May 10, 1945; 5.
      - Miller to Julius Emspak Regarding Dues and Veterans, July 20, 1945; 6.
      - Miller to James Matles Regarding Skilled Workers' Wages, January 8, 1952; 7.
      - Dorothy Phelps to UE Regarding Finances, January 5, 1945; 8.
      - Henry Ranch to Joseph Dermody Regarding Grievances, December 1, 1953; 9.
      - Ranch to Matles Regarding Finances, June 11, 1954; 10.
      - Ray Smith to Emspak Regarding Buffalo Conference, March 28, 1952; 11.
      - Smith to Joseph Turkowski Regarding Grievances and Arbitration, July 1952; 12.
      - E.W. Sole to Matles Regarding Business Agent, July 6, 1953; 13.
      - Trudi Southern to Emspak Regarding Westinghouse Strike, December 9, 1955; 14.
      - James Spillane to Fitzgerald Regarding Red-baiting, May 16, 1951; 15.
    - Local 1012 Pamphlet, For High Achievement Regarding Productivity, January 11, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Local 1012 Organization, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 68)
      - Charter Application, July 12, 1942; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Leo Turner, July 20, 1942; 2.
    - Local 1012 War Labor Board Order, 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 69)
      - Thomas Neblett to Carl Brant With Order, October 31, 1945; 1.
      - James Marsh to Joseph Dermody, February 16, 1946; 2.
    - Local 1012 Subsidy Request and Inter-union Rivalry, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 70)
      - Henry Fiering to James Matles, June 1, 1954; 1.
      - James Matles to Fiering, June 3, 1954; 2-3.
    - Local 1012 Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 71)
      - George Dodson to Julius Emspak Regarding Check-offs, April 17, 1943; 1.
      - Joseph Dermody to William Elconin Regarding Skilled Trades and Wages, December 14, 1951; 2.
      - Elconin to James Matles Regarding Staff Finances, July 27, 1953; 3.
    - Local 1012 Fireman's Insurance Co., 1970 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Local 1012 Strike, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Local 1012 Legislative Committee and Political Action, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Local 1012 Correspondence, 1958-1979 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Local 1012 Miscellaneous, 1969-1980 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Local 1012 Company Bulletins, 1976-1981 (Box 3, Folder 77-78)
    - Local 1012 Obsolete Supplements, 1971-1976 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Local 1012 Union Flyers, 1969-1981 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Local 1012 Ontario GE Arbitration, 1968-1970 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Local 1012 Ontario GE Arbitration Hearing, 1968-1970 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Local 1012 Ontario Criminal Cases, 1968-1970 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Local 1012 Ontario GE Charges, 1968-1970 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Local 1012 Ontario Injunction and Contempt Casefiles, 1968-1970 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Local 1012 Ontario Unemployment Compensation Cases, 1968-1970 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Local 1012 Ontario, CA, 1956-1967 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Local 1013
    - Local 1013 Organization, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Charter Application, December 1, 1942; 1.
      - Leo Turner to Julius Emspak, December 8, 1942; 2.
      - Emspak to Turner, December 11, 1942; 3.
      - Martin Hourihan to Emspak, July 30, 1943; 4.
      - Emspak to Hourihan, August 24, 1943; 5.
  - Local 1014
    - Local 1014 Strikes, Subsidies and Other Monies, 1973-1979 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Local 1014 Sanger, CA, General Cable Corporation Correspondence, 1979-1983 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Local 1015
    - Local 1015 Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Local 1015 Glendale and Dominguez, CA, Carol Cable Strike, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Local 1015 Strikes, Subsidies, and Other Monies, 1978-1985 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Local 1015 Constitution Correspondence, 1969-1979 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Local 1016
    - Local 1016 Tuscon Correspondence, 1973-1981 (Box 4, Folder 8-9)
    - Local 1016 Tuscon Supplements, 1974-1979 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Local 1016 Tuscon Miscellaneous, 1973-1981 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Local 1016 Strikes, Subsidies, and Other Monies, 1973-1979 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Local 1016 Tuscon Westinghouse Electric Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Local 1400
    - Local 1400 Officers Lists, July 8, 1937-December 18, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Local 1400 Membership Lists, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Local 1400 Incoming Correspondence, 1942-1945 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Joseph Dermody to Jean Sutherland Regarding Negotiations, May 8, 1944; 1.
      - Secretary of Julius Emspak to Frank Aninger Regarding Officers, November 11, 1942; 2.
      - Emspak to Sutherland Regarding American Communications Association, October 4, 1944; 3.
      - Emspak to George Carroll Regarding GE Service, December 28, 1944; 4.
      - Emspak to Sutherland Regarding Amalgamation of Locals 1400 and 1412, February 5, 1945; 5.
      - Emspak to Sutherland Regarding Amalgamation of Locals 1400 and 1412, August 24, 1945; 6.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Sutherland Regarding Amalgamation, July 28, 1945; 7.
      - Fitzgerald to John Nearney Regarding Amalgamation and Local 1412, August 10, 1945; 8.
    - Local 1400 Outgoing Correspondence, 1938-1948 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - Peter Apel to Julius Emspak Regarding Amalgamation of Locals 1400, 1410, and 1411, July 16, 1942; 1.
      - Frank Avingier to Emspak Regarding Officers and Membership, November 8, 1942; 2.
      - Avingier to Emspak Regarding Contracts, February 13, 1943; 3.
      - E. Buhle to Emspak Regarding Conscription, August 16, 1943; 4.
      - George Carroll to Emspak Regarding GE Service Shop and Local 1412, December 15, 1944; 5.
      - John Fernandes to UE Regarding Officers, October 1941; 6.
      - Fernandes to Emspak Regarding Amalgamation of Locals 1400 and 1411 and Political Action, June 1942; 7.
      - Marie Heiner to Emspak Regarding Officers, April 6, 1938; 8.
      - Heiner to Emspak Regarding Wages, March 15, 1939; 9.
      - Heiner to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, March 30, 1939; 10.
      - Heiner to Emspak Regarding Officers, December 1, 1939; 11.
      - John Klinger to Emspak Regarding Officers, August 23, 1943; 12.
      - Klinger to Emspak Regarding Unemployment and Finances, January 8, 1945; 13.
      - Klinger to Emspak Regarding United Steelworkers of America Inter-union Rivalry and Heintz and Kaufman, March 22, 1945; 14.
      - Klinger to Emspak Regarding USWA Inter-union Rivalry and Heintz and Kaufman, April 5, 1945; 15.
      - Klinger to Emspak Regarding GE Service and Local 1412, May 18, 1945; 16.
      - John Nerney to Emspak Regarding Staff Members and Organization, December 27, 1944; 17.
      - Frances Pacheco to Fitzgerald Regarding Constitutions, December 14, 1943; 18.
      - Jean Sutherland to George Dermody Regarding Contracts, May 6, 1944; 19.
      - Sutherland to Emspak Regarding Unemployment and Organization at Eitel McCullough, January 12, 1948; 20.
      - Sutherland to Emspak Regarding GE Service and Local 1412, February 8, 1945; 21.
      - Dorothy Tampas to Emspak Regarding Officers, August 25, 1943; 22.
      - Tampas to Emspak Regarding Address Change, October 12, 1943; 23.
    - Local 1400 Notices of Delinquency and Suspension, November 1937-January 1938 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Local 1400 Per Capita Reports, July 1937-July 1938 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Local 1400 Dues Statement, 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Local 1400 Publications, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - Army Navy Production Award Souvenir Pamphlet Regarding Heintz and Kaufman, October 1943; 1.
      - Radio Tube, December 27, 1943; 2.
    - Local 1400 Pacific Meter Negotiations, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 22)
      - Leo Fagerhaugh to James Matles, January 19, 1942; 1.
      - Negotiating Committee to F.H. Payne, February 2, 1942; 2.
      - Edwin Beal to Norton McKean, February 16, 1942; 3.
      - McKean to Beal, February 25, 1942; 4.
      - McKean to Beal, February 27, 1942; 5.
      - Beal to Hugh Harley, March 2, 1942; 6.
    - Local 1400 Amalgamation of Locals 1011 and 1400, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 23)
      - Julius Emspak to Carl Brandt, June 8, 1942; 1.
      - Brandt to Emspak, June 29, 1942; 2.
      - Secretary of Emspak to Brandt, July 1, 1942; 3.
      - Emspak to Brandt, July 8, 1942; 4.
      - Articles of Amalgamation, July 1942; 5.
    - Local 1400 Exide Negotiations, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 24)
      - Carl Brandt to L.O. Meyers, March 10, 1943; 1.
      - Carl Bersing to James Matles, March 22, 1943; 2.
      - Bersing to Brandt, March 22, 1943; 3.
      - Matles to Brandt, April 1, 1943; 4.
      - Average Wage Increases, 1943; 5.
      - Average Hourly Increases, 1943; 6.
    - Local 1400 Vacations, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 25)
      - Marcella Ryan to Leo Jandreau, November 19, 1943; 1.
      - Jandreau to Ryan, November 29, 1943; 2.
    - Local 1400 GE Service Transfer, 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      - Julius Emspak to Marcella Wood, December 28, 1944; 1.
      - Emspak to Wood, January 10, 1945; 2.
      - Wood to Emspak, January 15, 1945; 3.
      - Wood to Emspak, January 17, 1945; 4.
      - Wood to Emspak, April 11, 1945; 5.
    - Local 1400 Amalgamation of Locals 1400 and 1412, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 27)
      - Carl Brandt to Julius Emspak, January 26, 1945; 1.
      - Emspak to Marcella Wood, March 28, 1945; 2.
      - Wood to Emspak, April 3, 1945; 3.
      - Emspak to Brandt, April 11, 1945; 4.
      - Brandt to Emspak, April 21, 1945; 5.
      - Brandt to Albert Fitzgerald, July 24, 1945; 6.
      - Brandt to Fitzgerald, August 9, 1945; 7.
      - Fitzgerald to Brandt, August 10, 1945; 8.
      - Wood to Emspak, August 24, 1945; 9.
    - Local 1400 Miscellaneous, 1937-1945 (Box 4, Folder 28)
      - American Meter Statement of Policy, July 1937; 1.
      - Contract Proposal Regarding American Meter, 1937; 2.
      - Contract Proposal Regarding American Meter, 1941; 3.
      - Marcella Ryan to Julius Emspak, July 21, 1943; 4.
      - Ballot, December 1943; 5.
      - Ryan to Emspak Regarding Address Change, July 3, 1944; 6.
      - Ed Barlow to UE Regarding American Communications Association, September 1, 1944; 7.
      - Petition Regarding GE Service and Local 1412, February 13, 1945; 8.
  - Local 1401
    - Local 1401 Incoming Correspondence, James Haffey to UE Regarding Dues and Factionalism, November 19, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Local 1401 Outgoing Correspondence, Julius Emspak to James Haffey Regarding Dues, December 2, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Local 1412
    - Local 1412 Constitutions, November 1941 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Local 1412 Contracts, 1942-1945 (Box 4, Folder 32)
      - General Cable, August 1, 1942; 1.
      - Gardner Electric, August 1, 1945; 2.
    - Local 1412 Officers Lists, February 17, 1940-February 3, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Local 1412 Membership Resolutions, 1938-1948 (Box 4, Folder 34)
      - Membership Resolution Regarding Staff Members, September 30, 1938; 1.
      - Membership Resolution Regarding Political Action, April 2, 1948; 2.
    - Local 1412 Sandra Martin Incoming Correspondence, 1946-1950 (Box 4, Folder 35)
      - Janet Barish to Sandra Martin Regarding Finances, May 29, 1946; 1.
      - Barish to Martin Regarding Finances, October 18, 1946; 2.
      - Barish to Martin Regarding Publications, June 23, 1947; 3.
      - Bill Cahn to Martin Regarding Publicity, February 23, 1946; 4.
      - Julius Emspak to Martin Regarding Organization of White Collar Workers, Jun 15, 1944; 5.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding Inter-union Rivalry and General Cable, July 11, 1944; 6.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding Veterans and Dues, August 9, 1944; 7.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding Veterans and Dues, October 16, 1944; 8.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding General Cable Organization and Office Workers, December 20, 1944; 9.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding General Cable Office Organization, January 15, 1945; 10.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding Withdrawal Cards, September 20, 1945; 11.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding UE Policy Conference, April 29, 1946; 12.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding Strikes, May 8, 1946; 13.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding Strikes, May 16, 1946; 14.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding American Meter Negotiations, June 11, 1946; 15.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding Radio Broadcasts, May 26, 1947; 16.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding Grievances and Factionalism, August 8, 1947; 17-18.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding General Cable and Unemployment, August 11, 1947; 19.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding General Cable Strike, August 13, 1947; 20.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding Finances and Wages, July 21, 1948; 21.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding Finances, August 28, 1950; 22.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding Dues, December 1, 1950; 23.
      - Emspak to Martin Regarding Strikes, December 20, 1950; 24.